Film Name: Doraemon
It's good if it's so
If it can come to true it'll b nice
Different dreams
all can be arrived
The mysterious pocket
will compass it for you
I want to fly freely
Come on, use the dragonfly
Ah~Ah~Ah~ I love Doraemon most
(Air Diamonds manufacturing machine )
I'm back
Mom
You're back
You opened my drawer again
What're you saying
There's much waste in it
It's like rubbish
You'd tidy them up
It's excuse In fact morn is
looking for the paper of duck
What's up Nobita
You've found
I changed the place where I hid the
paper But I'm afraid it'll be found
You're wrong, why do you hide it
But...
I can understand you
You don't want the drawer raked over
Right?
What'll I do?
Build a wall in that room
It's impossible
To build what wall?
It can be done
How about it?
This is
Air Diamonds manufacturing machine
What's
Come to have a try
Nobita Come here
The air which could not be see by eyes
forms nugget here
It's so If we use the
Air Diamonds manufacturing machine
You made so much
Morn can't come close to my table
even she's powerful
I worry about it
What'll I do
if the paper in the drawer's found
It's coming
There's only one entrance here
Nobita Don't hide it
Show it to mom
It's strange
Damn
You remember
Succeed Succeed Succeed
There's no problem
I'll go out to play
Doraemon
But if I go out,
I'll be found by my father
It's nothing, I've
Air Diamonds manufacturing machine
Good It's OK
I'll go now Doraemon
ls Nobita alright
Then...
What will we play
It's Suneo
Hey Nobita, boob
How do you feel
It's painful!
What a pain... Damn...
Nobita, that guy
What a pain What's up
I don't know about Nobita's situation
Please wait a minute
Air Diamonds resumes every hour ()
Terrible! I ought to advise Nobita!
Nobita why are you happy
Jian
Nobita What's this
No Nothing
Don't you obey my order
Yes
Damn
Stand there
Don't run Don't run
What a pain...
It's raining
It's rainbow
Well Make this climb the rainbow
Climb taller and taller
The rainbow“ disappear
Let me have a try
I'll see how high I can climb
It's troublesome
where's Nobita?
Maybe you can climb higher
than Fuji Mountain
I want to go to toilet
Bad Go down
It'll be bad if I miss my step
Help
Doraemon Thank you for help me
The pine tree is great
Is it raining
I want to go to toilet
But it doesn't need
My back is hot It means...
Ah, I lost to you
( Continue Atomizer)
I've drawn it many times
But I still can't find the sense
Damn
I can't manage it
What do you mean
You give it up at one blow
are you a man
But Dahe battleship?»
really hard to draw
Many parts are too micromesh
What I want to draw is the Dahe
sailing in the stormy sea
Let me see...
Why do you laugh
You look down upon me
Sorry, I'm very sorry
you draw the front part of the ship
I only do that?
Right, you'd do it carefully
I can work it out with all my affort
Is it finished
Is it OK
Er, OK
Catch it
Use the Continue Atomizer
Spray this
How about it then
Wow~
Cool!
After spraying this
I can see the picture
Spray this to the calendar
The summer picture will become fall
Spay more
It becomes winter
Interesting atomizer
It can be used in pictures
This is the photo which was taken
when I started school
Let's go on to see
Er, let's have a try
Don't see it anymore!
I want to try more
Whose family has more pictures
Let's go to the new money's home
You want to see my gallery
I beg you
Although they're
copies, they all rank first
It doesn't matter
What?
No, I mean the top-grade
is worthy of appreciating
Is it?
Let me pour some tea
Appreciate it carefully
It's dazzle
Let's start here
Will this man become old?
It falls down!
It's raining!
This one is also interesting
It's bad
This is a thinker
What's he thinking over?
Let me see
What, he's dozing
Which's the next one?
It's powerful!
Sorry for kept waiting for a long time
What're you doing!
My collection...
How will you compensate for
my collection
Bad boy
Go out Don't let me see you again
We overdid it
I also feel he's poor
It's better to play at home
How do you like that one?
It should be no problem
What're you doing
Don't play monkey tricks with pictures
There's mather's private money in it
Great, it's not lost
It's important 10,000 yuan
What's up?
It's not my business
(Take back the lost machine)
No way! It's no way!
Nobita Will you go out for walking?
It's so fine
It's waste to sleep in the morning
Let's go out to play baseball
Nobita!
What It's Doraemon
Come to play baseball
Doraemon
Thank you for your tendance
I'm over
I'll get zero in the test tomorrow
Are you always the same every time
No, it's kidding
The schoolwork You'll not
graduate from primary school
Work hard Don't get zero
No, we needn't go to school today
I'll be scolded by mother soon
Why?
Because I lost
the thing I shew to Shizuka...
What's it?
Mother's best platina ring
She's looking for it now
Where's it...
It's disappeared, it's disappeared
He'll let me tell the truth
and swear me like a trooper
He'll drive me out of home
I'll wander in the
street and die of hunger
I'm over
You're exaggerating
No
Doraemon, it's not you who
made the trouble So you so
I see
You believe that man like me die
the sooner the better
Damn
Nanwuemitoufu
What a pain
No way
Let me help Nobita think about it
What's this
Take back the lost machine
Are you ready
Think about the shape of the lost ring
Ring, Ting"-
It's not so
Ah It's this one
It's this one Great
Return it to morn
Nobita go to school without worry
Thank you
Doraemon It's because of me
that mom did scold me
Right
Can it find anything lost
It can as long as
you remember the shape
Can I borrow it
I want to stick on the 10 yuan
lost yesterday
10 yuan 10 yuan...
Succeed!! It comes out!
My 10 Yuan
It's a dream to meet you again
OK Next one is 1,000 Yuan
1,000 Yuan 1,000 Yuan
It doesn't appear
Impossible, when did you lost it?
When... it... I didn't lost it
I spent it
No kidding
Read carefully, bad Nobita
Don't be angry
You won't change the result tomorrow
even you try your best today
I won't help you
Sorry, Doraemon
Don't scold me
Go on... ls there any other thing lost?
There's one
The plane model taken by Jian
the year before last
Succeed!
I'll call out all the things
lost before
The stuff I lost come out
one after another
This is the feeding-bottle
I liked most before
I don't care others' response
I still used it when
I was in the kindergarten
The taste brings me
to that period of time
It's really happy then
I wasn't urged to read every day
I wish that
I could have that time again
Nobita
Nobita you can recall the past time
but you'd do that after you grow up
You'd look into the future
and march forward
Future?
Don't disturb my business
My future is dark
I'm so climsy
and everything I did failed
Bad He lost confidence
I hope it'll go on forever
The sternaspidae which grandma gave me
She's so gentle then
I fell down in the yard at that time
Look The sternaspidae's stood up
Nobita can stand by himself too
Grandma, you can't get up,
You're ill now
How can I sleep
when I hear Nobita's crying
sorry
Nobita The sternaspidae's great
No matter how many times it falls down
it can stand itself
You'd learn from it
and to be a boy who can always
stand up himself when he falls down
Grandma won't worry about you then
I'll be the sternaspidae
I promise you
Soon grandma died
Grandma, sorry, I'd not self-degrade
I'll stand up myself in the future
Maybe I'll fall down many times
but I'll stand up
Don't worry, grandma
Nobita, cheer up and go out to play
Wow...
lt'a too noisy Doraemon,
I'm reading
What happened on earth
( The Pre-requisite Antenna )
It's painful
Are you insulted by Jian again?
You're too fainthearted
No, I only walked as usual
and suddenly something fell down
from the above
I lifted my head to see what it is
You're exaggerating
People will run away or catch it
when something falls down
It's too late when
it falls down on you
You'd preclude it
Stand stablely
before loosing your footing
or pick it up before it fall down
You're always too slow
you're always cursing me
I'm not God
It's impossible that I can have measures
before anything happens
Yeah, it's possible
It's OK
to use the pre-requisite antenna
You will get warning
before anything happens
Something will happen
What's it, is it a bad one
or a good one
I don't know what's it
But I can't help moving
Why do you bring out my pillow?
I don't know
But it'll be put into use soon
Doraemon
Cheer up
Have you found the effect
of the antenna
The pillow kept my head from damaging
It's nothing
Don't expect too much Have a try
Nobita
What's up? Morn
You take chutty And then?
You divide it into two parts,
and mass them up
and put it into your ears
What am I doing?
Sit down
How many times I'll repeat till
you understand, you're in Grade Four
He's often scolded
Nobita, are you listening
Look at mom's eyes carefully
You're too naughty
You never listen to mom
and your mark is always so poor...
I heard nothing So it doesn't matter
Dad's looking for you
Here
Lighter?
Does anyone know
where my lighter is
Ah?
I'm always looking for him
How do you know it
I don't know
It's incredible
Ah, is it the pre-requisite antenna
May I use it
I'll go out now
I see Dad is a careless man
It's useful
Look, he's making preparation
I found
the telescope and the trousers
and the box
Why must I take them
I don't know
Do as the indication of the antenna
There'll be no mistakes
Take care
I'm a little worried, I don't know
what'll happen on my way
Mr.Ye, what's the matter with you?
Your trousers are all wet
Fortunately I take the trousers
Excuse me
Sir, you remain what you were
Thank you
You're welcome, relax yourself
It's been peaceful recently
That's the best
What?
Is it a fire
I can see the smoke far away
Where's it?
Let me have a look Ah, it's true
The fire is very strong
It's so terrible
It's fearful
Do you always take it with you
No
Your bad habit of Roman holiday
remains unchanged
Yeah
( He's still different)
Would you have a
taste the cake I made
Does it fit you
You're welcome
Take it please
Then I'll help myself
It's nice
It's the first time for me
to have so good cake
Shall I look for a box
and take some for your family
No, thank you
You needn't do so
To put it into my box is OK
You're welcome
You're very considerate
You're appreciated
ls everything taken put into use
Why do you get angry
And I bring much delicious food
(Sound Nugget)
Is it Jian again
Why are you always bullied by others
Because I'm
shorter and thinner than he
I'm weak and have no strength
Doraemon,
do you have any good idea
No way
You made no progress
because you always depend on me
He's really poor
But it's no way
You can only cry louder than others...
Right, use your voice
Voice?
This is sound nugget
Medicine?
No You know I don't like it
It's not spicy nor bitter
Have a try
There's no way to deal with you There's
only a little and it's valuable
You're too atrabilious
And then? Nothing happened
Wait and see
What's this?
This is medicine solidified of shout
You can shout when Jian'll beat you
It's so Then
Let me have a try
stop
Ah~~
It's painful
The medicine will be lose its effect
if the sound is too loud
It can only last 30 mins
The medicine's only...
There's only a little medicine
I'll take the rest
Then I'll rival Jian
I'll teach him a lesson next time
Nobita, the box is caught by the tree
Could you help me take it down
OK
It's here
Oops? It's so high?
It'd be enough
Yeah!
Nobita, your ability's curious,
I respect you very much
Thank you...
Do it for me again
Let me see
Thief!
Help me to catch the thief!
Hey!
You're great, Nobita
I'll be shy
Bad
What's the matter, uncle
The important signboard becomes bad
OK, let me manage it
You...?
Noodles!
OK
This one is nice It'd be OK
Thank you
You did great help for me, I'll invite
you to have some noodles
I earn a bottle of noodles
It's good to have a specialty
Don't forget your things
Hey! You forgot your belongings
It's Nobita
He's doing strange things
I'll report it
Sound nugget is helpful to man
I begin to have confidence
It's Suneo
Suneo
It's Nobita
He'!
What's this
Wow!
Hey!
Who broke my bonsai
Don't shout
What?
Nobita's mad
How dare you accept gifts freely
And then you were defeated
What're you saying?
I become angry
as long as I think of him
Go to bully him
I didn't meet Jian and Suneo
when I have ability
Nobita
When I want to insult a man
And you'll be the first one
I'm seeking for you
I'll not lose to you this time
He's so aggressive
Don't be surprised at it No don't
be frightened if you're defeated
Jian is a fat boob
Ah? He didn't come out?
Bad! It's too much
The medicine doesn't work
Stand there
Damn Where did he gone
He'll be beaten when he's found by me
It's dangerous
You can't rival him
if you don't take medicine
He disappeared?
What'll I do?
Don't lick the water on the ground
It's dirty Let's go
No, don't quarrel with him
Doggie
He did as Nobita
I know the liquid just now is...
It's in... It's found
Splash all of it
Nobita's timid, come out
I'll dressing down you
What'll I do? Escape or hide?
Shizuka Have you seen Nobita
I saw him long ago
Don't cheat me It's true that
I didn't see him recently
Shizuka's bullied
OK, I decided,
I'll go out to be stroked
I can't bring Shizuka trouble
Nobita's coming Jian
I'll kill him
What? What's up?
The dog's like Nobita
Ah?
How dare you look down upon me
like that The dog
I'll teach you a lesson first
It's too heavy
Thank you for beating him for me
Don't pile toies there
I'm back
What's this? Ah! It's Doraemon
Doraemon
It's so cold
What'll we do
(Star of Hope)
What? What's up?
What's the matter with you
Doraemon
Pull me out
Help me
Haha
You cumulate so much
It's like a warehouse
Are these all will be put into
the almighty pocket
It's out of expect
Yes, I want to repair it
Throw it away
It's a pity to do that Give it to me
No, they all can't be used
Give me one, it doesn't matter
No
The umbrella is nice
That's an umbrella
And this?
Brawler glove
It seems like common boxing glove
You can fight wearing it
And this one?
Almighty wooden foot ware
It's a good scene
Only when four men put on it together
can they walk
They're all useless
Throw them away
I've said that at the beginning
Throw them around
What's this
It's beautiful
That's Star of Hope
Give me this one
No, no way
It'd be tossed out
What a pity
If you give it to
Shizuka, he'll be glad
No, Bury all
Doraemon always works carefully
It's OK
Star of Hope...
What? Star of Hope?
Every dream can be realized
OK Dig it out
Move, Dig it out
before Nobita does it
You dare to glom it with me?
It...
Don't prevent us
Damn I'll tell Doraemon it
Suneo and Jian...?
Will be taken by them two
OK, we needn't that
No, you'd find a way
Let's do it this way
That's settled
It's buried very deep
I can't bear it
It's too deep, we can't finished
Nobita can't finish it
The shining Star of Hope
come to me
Succeed
Hey, give it to me
No~
Don't run, stop
Hide me, Star of Hope
Ah? Where's he?
Where is he gone?
Damn, I'll not
forgive it if I find him
Why I hide here, it's terrible
The star will realize all my hopes
What's the next hope
I've many hopes
Star, come over
Jian! Bad!
Doraemon, get up
It's too noisy, what's up?
The star's stolen by Jian
What'll we do?
It's good
Good?
When the star's
asked, it'll come there
and it usually makes mistakes
Shining Hope of Star
Give me big diamond
I mean diamond, not wheels and trees
Star, come over
I'll love you
Go on...What hope
shall I make you realize it
I've many models
I sot m.
Shining Hope of Star
Give me more money
What're these? Stop
Don't run away
What're you doing
Ah, the perfume's used up
Give me perfume, do you know
Mom, don't worry
Perfume's coming
Mom's too glad
Shining Hope of Star
Give mom perfume
What
Does he mistake perfume as flood
What're you doing!
Sorry
Damn, it's all Nobita's mistake
to dig this out
OK! I'll teach him a lesson
Shining Hope of Star
Let it rain in Nobita's room
Doraemon, I want to have something
It's sweets
Doraemon, it'll be nice
if it rain gong cake
I think the Hope of star must be wrong
The shining
$11878
Make our hope come to true
( Become thunder)
The cloud is so heavy
It rains suddenly
We can't play football
The rain in the dusk won't last long
Let's play chess before it stops
It's Jian's turn
It's too noisy
I'm thinking
It's shining
and thundering
It's coming
What a terrible thunder
It's shining again
The thunder's around there
Is it the direction to Nobita's
Nobita
Ah?
Nobita disappeared
It's strange, he's here just now
OK I see
Nobita's fearful of it,
so he hid himself
He's there
Right
Open m.
OK
He's really in it
Nobita's a timid
Are you afraid of thunder so much
Yes, he is
What? Will you go in laugh then?
You're useless
No way, I hate thunder most
It's only common electricity
I know
But I'm in fear of it
You're useless
Doraemon
Do you have a way to let me
not be afraid of it
I've no method to deal with you
Let me see...
OK! Let's use this one!
Let it help you
What's that?
It's cloud
Although it's small, it's powerful
Have a try
Nobita
You can't run away
It's your turn this time
Is it alright
The string's switch, pull it
But... I'm greatly scared
You became what you were, be quick
But...
Hurry!
No, you want to run again
Didn't I say you can't escape
Once again
Come, be a man
It's frightening...
It's better now
Thank you, Doraemon
Great
You won't be afraid when it thunders
after you're used to it
But you only have the confidence
I feel it's funny
OK I'll let you see
Nobita, help me bring the match
Dad, can I light with it
What's that
Can it light
Yeah, it's a electric lighter
Really, let me have a look
How about it, it really can light
Boob
It's a small failure
Jian's bullying others
OK, let me teach him a lesson
It's interesting
Jian
What Nobita What are you doing
Give the controller to him,
don't bully the weak
Do you want to help him
How dare you say that, timid
I'm not afraid of thunder any longer
Give it to him
Don't be wordy Keep off
OK, there's no way
I'll let the justice thunder come out
Mom, help me
Great
Nobita's fearful of thunder
and he's trembling next to our home
When we talk about you, you come
It's Nobita OK Laugh at him
Suneo
Nobita, is your navel there
What do you mean?
Let me tell you,
I'm not afraid of thunder now
You're cheating us,
you were obviously trembling then
You're a big tricker
No, I didn't cheat you
Will you have a try
Interesting You have a try
I'll see how prove it
Begin, begin
OK, let me show you
Thus everyone knows
Nobita doesn't fear thunder
It's all due to Doraemon
Nobita, you're back
It's dark inside,
why don't you turn the light
Curious There're two wires
That's...
Bad
Who played the monkey trick
Mom, it's thundering, escape!
You two stop
Damn, where did they hide
Mom's angry You'd find a way
No
When the thunder comes,
mom's the most fearful
( XYZ Light Camera )
He'!
If you want to see the book,
take out money and buy it
You read here every day
you'll affect my business
How dare you say that
There's only half of it...
What did you said
When you read them all,
my business's over
The child's unshameful
It's a pity
I read it for a week continuously
and finished half of it
I'll not go there at present
But the Captain J in the book is cool
Our goal's that star
Captain, bad
There're a huge group of falling stars
on the right
Don't worry, calculate their track
No, the computer doesn't work now
They'll crash in a minute
Be calm, let me operate
We must not die in space
Sit well
Break the little stars into pieces
with thunder gun
ls the data of attack worked out
It's terrible,
I never saw so huge percussion
The second is damaged
And the magnetic field's wrong too
You draw me sharp
when it's most interesting
The book is taken away by
the boss of the book store
I want to see the next part
What's the matter with you
I really want to know the result
of Captain J
It's simple
Going on reading is OK
Can you let me read standing here
Which book?
This one
It comes again
It's OK not to steal it
Yeah... yes
It's finished
XYZ Light Camera
Put the book towards me
What do you take a picture
of the cover for
Excuse me
You're welcome
Thank you for coming
I feel a little strange
It's Captain Jian!
Right, it's a camera which can
take the content inside
Every page can be taken
Great
Doraemon
It comes again
He'd have his way
Lend it to me
Nobita's always careless,
I worry about him
It's a piece of cake
Please accept it
Thank you
OK, take it
What're you saying, Nobita
Go out to play
You'd not say that so clearly
She said it's chicken feed herself
Morning
ls nobody in
It's troublesome
Let me help you to see
if there's someone
What'll I do?
Let me manage it
He's sleeping
Without clothes?
Don't mind, I'm only doing you a favor
Really
Thank you
I'll photo his nude body
There're many interesting things
Give the sweets to me
I didn't take it
Suneo's bullying the weak
OK!
It's as I expected
Suneo, it's useless to hide
It's under the
shirt and near the navel
How could you know
Don't bully the weak Look
What's this
It's shameful
Morning
Shizuka, where're you going
I'll go to study
Your camera's so special,
take a picture for me
OK
No, no way
Why'!
I can't do it even you beg me
Hum, you can't waste film
You're mean
Why you say that
I don't take for you
because I think of Shizuka
Do you have the same feeling,
Doraemon
Don't involve me
Yeah, it's better not to take it
But... help her take one
It's required herself
You're too curious
I'm not responsible for the result
Shizuka
Wait
I'm not so mean as you said
Will you take photos for me
I'm very glad
I'd make up if I'd known
you'd take picture for me
It doesn't need
What does it mean?
No, I mean Shizuka's beautiful
with any clothes
Are you ready, I'll take it
OK
The distance isn't good
It's better to come close
It's OK
The clothes won't be taken then
You'd at least take the back
Don't always
say that strange words
Be quick
I see, I'll do it now
Ah, well
What's up?
There'll be a warning
if the film is used up
The one you took just now...
Of course it didn't succeed
Tiresome, you waste me much time
I'm angry
The film's used up,
the sense of lost... and relaxed
It's lucky that nothing happened
Great
Some faces-'re round
Some faces-'re long
Some faces' re square
Some faces-'re triangular
Weeping Angry
Fawning and requiring
You'll become a ghost who likes crying
But if you smile
Your face will become round